

TANET LIMSUMANGKOLKUL

Check Out My Portfolio

CONTACT



0982846992



jaytanet@gmail.com



56 road rama2 alley 51 Subdistrict thakam District Bang Khun Thian Bangkok 10150

SKILL

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- JQuery
- TawinCss
- Antd
- Bootstrap
- React
- NodejsPython
- Fytholi
- Express
- PHP
- Postman

- MySQL
- SQL Server
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- Postgres
- AWS
- Thai Data Clound
- Docker
- GIT

LANGUAGE

- English
- Thai

PROFILE

I am interested in working as a Full Stack Developer, with the ability to develop both frontend and backend systems. I also have experience deploying systems to the cloud using services such as AWS and Thai Data Cloud, ensuring that systems operate efficiently and reliably. Additionally, I possess strong teamwork, communication skills, and a commitment to learning new technologies to continuously improve system performance.

EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer | Rama 2 Medical Group

(Sep 2023 - Present)

Get user requirements and designed the user interface, APIs, and backend for Anyhos system using Node, is and Express. Integrated Firebase notifications, payment systems, and external APIs (Krungthai Bank, Chiline, LINE Notify). Designed database structures using Firebase and MongoDB. Enhanced security with JWT tokens and encryption. Managed deployment on AWS, including ELB for the backend and S3 with Route 53 for the frontend. Developed admin management system such as patient management, payment and report.

Programmer | Bizpotential co. ltd

(Mar 2022 - Nov 2022)

Developed system MRTA HR, TSRI HR, CRA_ERP_EDU, MUIC, and SIRIRAJ. Responsible for implementing new features such as email notification systems, Import excel data to system, Generation transcript to Word format. welfare system, as well as submission and approval flows.

EDUCATION

Mittraphon Business Administration (2012-2016)

• Business Computer

Rajamangala University of Technology Krungthep (2017-2020)

• Information System